INNOCENT THOMAS

Innthomas00158@gmail.com
1 Abasi Orok Street, Calabar, Cross River State
08036184619
https://github.com/innthomas
www.linkedin.com/in/innocent-thomas-aca-9ba69911a

OBJECTIVES

I have worked in the micro-finance sub-sector of the finance industry for about a decade. Half of this period till date, I spend as an entrepreneur, designing products and strategies to meet the needs of nano, micro and small scale businessmen and women within my niche. As a result, I have developed a close commitment to and passion for small business management, financing, as well as strategic development.

Furthermore, my professional training in accountancy, finance and strategic management under the distinguished Institute of Chartered Accountants of Nigeria (ICAN), has honed my skills and prepared me for even greater challenges within the profession. Hence, I have the competence and ability to add value in the accounting or management discipline of any organization with profit or non-profit orientation.

Finally, I wish to add that my proficiency in python programming and SQL endows me with the capacity to analyze and manage data. I can also use excel as well as Sage 50 to complete assigned tasks.

EDUCATION

Institute of Chartered Accountants of Nigeria (ICAN)

2018 Associate Chartered Accountant (ACA)

Membership Number NO 046759

NATIONAL TEACHERS INSTITUTE, KADUNA

2012 Post Graduate Diploma in Education(PGDE)

NIGERIAN INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT(NIM)

2010 MEMBER NIGERIAN INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT(MNIM)

UNIVERSITY OF CALABAR, CALABAR

2009: B.Agric (Soil Science)

EXPERIENCE

CITY LEAD,

DATASCIENCE NIGERIA, YABA, LAGOS,

JAN 2020 - TILL DATE

Goodwill Microfinance Enterprise | Watt, Calabar Rd, Calabar

CEO 2013 - till date

FIRST ROYAL MICROFINANCE BANK LTD, 12 CHALMER STREET, CALABAR

Business Development officer, 2010-2013

GOVERNMENT GIRLS COLLEGE, MABERA, SOKOTO

Teacher 2009-2010

CHRISTIAN HIGH SCHOOL, 28 ATAKPA STREET, CALABAR

Teacher 2008-2009

SKILLS

- Python Programming: Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Flask, Django
- Flutter Programming
- Database Management: MS Access, MYSQL, POSTGRESQL
- MS EXCEL
- Microsoft Office
- Business and Financial Management
- Strategic Planning

- Risk and Credit Management.
- Project Management

HOBBIES

Reading,

Poetry,

Socio-economic commentator, and

Jugging.

REFEREES

Philip Udoimeh,
 Sturer Federal University of Te

Lecturer, Federal University of Technology, Yola, Adamawa State 08064357490

• Paul Bassey Okon PhD

Lecturer, University of Calabar, Calabar, Cross River State. pbokon@yahoo.com